<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Commercial Real Estate and Commercial Law]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Commercial Real Estate and Commercial Law]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/cre/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 19:08:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/cre/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time Costs Money and Kills Deals]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Time Costs Money and Kills Deals</h1><p>Scenario 1: The tenant and the landlord have finally agreed to essential business terms through a month long back and forth negotiation. So, the terms of the final LOI are incorporated into the actual lease by the Landlord, which is 50 pages long of dense legalese, and another 40 pages of exhibits. The tenant's attorney marks up this extremely pro-landlord lease and sends it back to the landlord's attorney. Only a couple of changes are accepted in this go around. The attorneys keep negotiating, while undoubtedly telling their clients that the other side is  being completely unreasonable and that that the lease, as the other side wants, gives their own side to much liability. All of this back and forth takes an additional 8 weeks until the final lease is signed, if at all. It took three entire months to negotiate the final LOI and lease, with thousands of dollars being paid to the attorneys.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/8d8daeec79a36a6bbd25de55a055436b98736455.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/cre/time-costs-money-and-kills-deals/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e89f2782-8658-4267-92a8-190cdde11db6</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 19:07:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About Benjamin Dalton]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About Benjamin Dalton</h1><p>Welcome to the Law Office of Benjamin Dalton. We specialize in commercial real estate and commercial law. As both a real estate attorney and real estate agent, Mr. Dalton helps  clients with acquiring and selling commercial real estate as well as with commercial leasing and negotiations. Having both the knowledge of the law and the market, Mr. Dalton is able to leverage both to the benefit of his clients.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/cre/about-benjamin-dalton/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">03a1b965-07c2-4b57-9de6-7e33017008ce</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 19:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome to the Law Office of Benjamin Dalton]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Welcome to the Law Office of Benjamin Dalton</h1><p>Welcome to our firm. We specialize in Commercial Real Estate and Commercial Law. Whether you are looking at acquiring or selling a commercial asset to needing assistance to negotiating a lease, you have come to the right place. Ben Dalton, the head of our firm is both a real estate lawyer and commercial real estate agent. In other words, he knows both the market and the law. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/6d75e737e74c231fc689054889b90a4aac48f3ee.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/cre/welcome-to-the-law-office-of-benjamin-dalton/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7250aa50-bd4b-429a-b274-3db66367234b</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 18:52:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>